Guide to the Robert Maynard Hutchins Papers 1884-2000
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company, 1944-1945 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company, 1944-1946 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company - Board of Directors - Monthly Report, 1944-1946 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company, 1945 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company, 1945-1950 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Association Commerce, 1930-1948 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Bar Association, The, 1930-1937 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Bar Association, The, 1939-1951 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Church Federation, 1939 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Chicago, City Manager Committee, 1936-1939 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Chicago, City of, 1938-1951 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Civil Liberties Committee, 1938-1947 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Club, The, 1933-1937 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Club, The, 1938-1945 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Club, The, 1944-1951 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Commonwealth Club, 1936-1937 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Commonwealth Club, 1938-1943 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Commonwealth Club, 1944-1950 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations, 1938-1950 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Chicago, D, 1929-1937 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Chicago, D, 1929-1939 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Federated Advertising Club, 1937-1945 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Hospital Council, 1937-1941 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Chicago, Junior Association of Commerce, 1931-1950 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Maroon, 1937-1950 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Chicago newspapers, 1932-1937 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Chicago newspapers, 1933-1951 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Chicago newspapers - Chicago Daily News, 1936-1937 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Chicago newspapers - Chicago Daily News, 1938-1950 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Chicago newspapers - Chicago Daily News (series of articles on Chicago), 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Recreation Commission, 1934-1935 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Recreation Commission, 1934-1936 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Recreation Commission, 1936-1937 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Recreation Commission, 1937 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Recreation Commission, 1937-1949 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Recreation Commission, 1939-1945 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Recreation Commission, 1945-1949 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Teachers Union, 1937-1945 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, The, 1934-1948 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Women's Club, 1937-1946 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Chicago World's Fair, 1932-1935 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Child Research Clinic, 1937-1948 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Child Study Association of America, 1937-1938 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Children's Scholarship League, 1938-1941 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - China, Chinese, 1938-1950 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - China - Christian Colleges - Emergency Committee, 1937 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - China - Christian Colleges - Emergency Committee, 1937-1939 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Christian, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Christian Century Magazine, 1943-1948 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1935-1946 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Christian Science Monitor - Reader's Digest article by John R. Tunis, 1944-1949 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Christians, George W., 1941-1942 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Church, 1938-1950 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Churchill, William, 1937 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Cincinnati, 1930-1947 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Committee for a County College, 1938-1950 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Citizens Committee for Planned Parenthood, 1938-1939 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Citizens Schools Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Citizens Schools Committee, 1938-1949 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Citizenship, 1940-1949 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Citizenship and Naturalization, Committee on, 1934-1936 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - City Club of Chicago, 1929-1937 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - City Club of Chicago, 1939-1951 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - City Manager League, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Civil Rights Federation, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Clark, Charles E., 1929-1939 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Clark, Charles E., 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Charles J., 1924-1926 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Fred G., 1940 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Grenville, 1936-1951 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Clark, William D., 1942-1949 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Clark and Clarke, 1936-1950 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Clark and Clarke, 1939-1950 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Clarksdale, 1937-1938 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Classics, A-Z, 1937 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Classics - List of 10, 1945-1947 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Classics - Requests for lists - A-G, 1938-1948 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Classics - Requests for lists - A-G, 1938-1948 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Classics - Requests for lists - H, 1938-1948 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Classics - Requests for lists - H-L, 1938-1948 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Classics - Requests for lists - M, 1938-1948 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Classics - Requests for lists - M-R, 1938-1948 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Classics - Requests for lists - S-Z, 1938-1948 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Claunch, Stanford Kingsley, 1939-1940 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland, 1929-1951 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland College (Western Reserve) - Great Books speech, 1947-1948 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Cleveland conference, 1936-1938 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland, The City Club of, 1937-1946 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Cloutier, F. A., 1935-1938 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Coca-Cola Company, 1935-1936 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Cockrell, Ewing, 1939-1946 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Coffman, Lotus D., 1937 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Cofrances, Humbert, 1939-1941 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Cohen, 1938-1948 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Alfred E., 1937-1939 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Cole, 1939-1949 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Cole, Stewart F., 1938-1939 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Coleman, 1943-1949 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Coles, L. F., 1941-1942 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - College, 1939-1951 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - College of the City of New York, 1930-1936 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - College Years, 1938 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Collier's Magazine - General, 1946-1950 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Collier's Magazine - December 30, 1944 issue, 1941-1946 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Collier's Magazine - June 9, 1945 issue, 1945-1947 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Collier's Magazine - "Let's Split the Education Atom" - December 7, 1946 issue, 1946-1947 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Collins, 1937-1942 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Colorado, 1939-1950 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Colorado Education Association, 1931-1934 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Columbia, 1938-1949 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1938-1973 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Columbia Law Review, 1926 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, 1931-1951 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University Hillman Lecture, November 21, 1950, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Columbus, 1937-1943 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Colvin, H. Milton, 1937-1947 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Colwell, Ernest Cadman, 1945-1974 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Colwell, Ernest Cadman, 1947 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Commercial and Financial Chronicle, 1943-1945 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Commercial Club, 1932-1937 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Commercial Club, 1938-1945 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Commercial Club - Notices of meetings, 1939-1951 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Commercial Club, 1942-1951 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Commission, 1941-1946 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1934-1935 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Commission of Inquiry on National Policy in International Economic Relations, 1935-1936 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Manpower, Automation, and Technology (includes other records), 1963-1964 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Commission on Manpower, Automation, and Technology (includes other records), 1964-1965 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Manpower, Automation, and Technology (includes other records), 1965-1968 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Committee for Concerted Peace Efforts, 1939 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100, 1944-1948 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Amnesty, 1946-1948 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Committee on "Participation by Lawyers as Citizens in Public Affairs," 1948 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Committees, 1939-1951 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Common Cause, 1947-1950 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Common Council for American Unity, 1940-1945 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Commonweal, The, 1939-1951 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Community, 1939-1950 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Community and War Fund - Special Gifts Division, 1943 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Community and War Fund - Special Gifts Division, 1943-1944 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Community Council, 1934-1936 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Community Fund of Chicago, Inc., 1933-1946 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Community Mobilization for Human Needs, 1937-1942 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Compton, Arthur, 1936-1947 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Conant, James B., 1938-1947 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Conference Board, The, 1941-1950 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy, and Religion, 1940 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy, and Religion, 1940-1943 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy, and Religion, 1941-1943 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy, and Religion, 1942-1951 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Congregational Christian Church Education Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Congresses, 1938-1948 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut, 1938-1950 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Conrady, Elsie, 1938-1939 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Consolidated Broadcasting System, 1938 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Constitution, 1936-1940 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Controllers Institute of America, 1948 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Cook, 1939-1951 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Cook, Thos. and Son, 1932-1938 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Cooke, Edmund W. (with election materials), 1952-1959 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Cooke, Thomas T., 1924-1927 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Cooper, 1938-1946 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Copeland, 1940-1941 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Copernican Quadricentennial National Committee, 1943 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Corey, Stephen M., 1936-1948 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Cormier, Margaret, 1939 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Cornell, 1938-1951 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Coronet Magazine, 1939-1950 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Cory, Herbert E., 1939-1941 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Cosmopolitan, 1929-1936 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, 1936-1937 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Coulborn, Rushton, 1936-1944 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Council Against Intolerance in America, 19388-1947 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1939-1946 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Councils, 1938-1950 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Countryside Lake, 1938-1946 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Courtney, 1940 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Cousins, Norman, 1954-1973 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Cox, 1934-1950 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Cox, George Clarke, 1933-1937 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Crane, 1939-1950 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Crane, George W., 1938-1940 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Crawford, Albert Beecher, 1938 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Creighton University, 1937-1938 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Cresap, Mark W., 1934-1950 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Crofts, F. S. and Company, 1941-1945 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Crosby Family, 1929-1935 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Cross, Neal M., 1938 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Crow and Crowe, 1938-1942 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Crowley, Patrick F., 1966-1976 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Crowther, Sir Geoffrey, 1957-1959 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Crumrine, Homer, 1941 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Culberton, Ely, 1944-1949 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Culver Military Academy, 1938-1944 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Cumming, Captain John W. W., 1942-1943 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Cunningham, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Cunningham, W. F., 1938-1943 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Current History, 1939-1943 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Curtis, 1940-1950 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Cushman, Robert E., 1939 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Cutler, 1939-1941 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Cyrus Fishermen's College, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1938-1950 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Dahlberg, Edward, 1958-1966 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Daily, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Daily Maroon, 1934-1937 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Daily News (Los Angeles), 1954-1955 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Dallas, 1938-1941 (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Danforth, William H., 1936-1946 (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - Dart, Justin W., 1938-1949 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Dart, Justin, 1945-1972 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Davenport, 1939-1950 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Davidson, 1939-1950 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Davis, 1933-1950 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Chester, 1951-1960 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Davis, Eugene, 1936-1942 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Davis, Eugene, 1942-1947 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Eugene, 1949-1950 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Jerome, 1923-1956 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Jerome, 1937-1951 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Davisson, Oscar, 1939-1950 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Davisson, Oscar and Daphne, 1949-1963 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Day, Edmund E., 1936-1949 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Deak, Francis, 1939-1940 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Deane, Charles J., 1938-1940 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Degrees (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - de Hovre, Dr. Fr., 1939 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - DeJouvenel, Bertrand, 1960-1977 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Delta, 1937-1949 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Denison, 1938-1948 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Dennis, 1940-1943 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Denver, University of, 1938-1950 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Deppe, W. P., 1940 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Derry, George Hermann, 1939-1947 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Der Zakarian, Aram, 1939-1942 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Des Moines, 1938-1948 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Desarc, Karlof, 1942 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Desvernine, Raoul E., 1938-1940 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Detroit, 1938-1949 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Devereux, Cherry, 1937-1939 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Devereux, Frederick L., 1933-1949 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Dewey, Charles S., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Dewey, John, 1943-1950 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Dexter, Lewis A., 1937-1949 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Dexter, Nina C., 1947-1948 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Dexter, Nina C., 1948 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Dexter, Nina C., 1948 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Dexter, Nina C., 1948-1949 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Dial Press, 1938-1950 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Dickson, Fagan, 1967-1976 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Dickinson, 1939-1945 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Dickinson, Frank G., 1938-1950 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Dillard University, 1937 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Dilworth, Richardson, 1923-1971 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Dilworth, Richardson, 1931-1950 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Dimock, Marshall E., 1937-1946 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Diserio, Matthew J., 1931-1947 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Dodd, William E., 1937-1938 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Doherty, 1939-1941 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Donnelly, 1938-1948 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Donnelly, Esther, 1947-1948 and undated (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Donovan, 1936-1945 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Dora B. Talbot, 1950 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Doubleday, Doran and Co., Inc., 1938-1949 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Dougherty, 1939-1940 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Douglas, 1939-1951 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Douglas, James H., 1938-1949 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Douglas James H., 1952-1977 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Douglas, William O., 1929-1937 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Douglas, William O., 1938-1951 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Douglas, William O., 1951-1965 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Douglas, William O., 1963-1969 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Douglas, William O., 1970-1974 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Douglas, William O., 1975-1980 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Drake, 1937-1943 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Drake, Henry L., 1939-1945 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Drake University, 1930-1937 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Draper, Benjamin, 1940-1949 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Driskill, John W., 1950 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Drown, Joseph W., 1963-1972 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Drown, Joseph W., 1972-1977 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Drucker, Peter F., 1939-1942 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Dubuque, 1943-1945 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Duell, Soan and Pearce, Inc., 1940-1945 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Duggan, 1941 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1938-1941 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Duncan, 1938-1951 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Dunkirk Society, 1948 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - DuPont, Paul, 1938 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Dutton, 1941-1950 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Duval, 1938-1943 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Dux, Dieter, 1942-1948 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Dye, George, 1948 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Dyes, O. F., 1941 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Dykstra, Clarence, 1940-1945 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Earlham College, 1938-1947 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - East, 1938-1948 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - East Tennessee Education Association, 1936-1946 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Eastern, 1940-1950 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Ohio Teachers Association, 1938-1942 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Eastman, 1938-1943 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Eaton, Cyrus S., 1939-1948 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Eaton, Cyrus and Anne, 1955-1962 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Eaton, Cyrus and Anne, 1962-1976 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Eaton, Harold T., 1939 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Eckart, Percy, 1938-1944 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Economic Club, 1937-1943 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Economic Club of Chicago, 1930-1936 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Economic Forum, 1934-1937 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Eddy, 1939-1942 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Edison, 1938-1946 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Education for Freedom, Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Education for Freedom, Inc., 1943-1944 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Education for Freedom, Inc., 1943-1944 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Education for Freedom - A-C, 1942-1950 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Education for Freedom - C-H, 1943-1949 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Education for Freedom - I-L, 1943-1944 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Education for Freedom - L-N, 1943 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Education for Freedom - O-S, 1943-1950 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Education for Freedom - S-Z, 1943-1948 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Education for Freedom - Louisiana State University Press, 1941-1949 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Educational, 1936-1951 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Educational Fund, Inc. (includes minutes, financial, and other records), 1944-1957 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Educational Fund, Inc. - Measure magazine, 1948-1949 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Educational Fund, Inc. - Gift material, 1944-1946 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Educational Fund, Inc. - Gift material, 1945-1948 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Educational Fund, Inc. - Gift material, 1949-1950 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Edwards, 1949-1950 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Egle, Joseph A., 1940 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Eichler, Edward, 1963-1964 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1954 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - El Paso, 1938-1946 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Elgin, 1938-1947 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Elias, Hans, 1942-1951 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Eliot, T. S., 1952-1953 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Elliot, John B., 1952-1957 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Elliot, John B., 1958-1959 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Elliot, John B., 1960-1966 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Elliot, John C., 1953-1962 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Elliot, John C., 1963-1977 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Elliott, 1940-1948 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Elliott, Edward C., 1938-1945 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Emergency, 1938-1944 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Emerson, 1939-1941 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Emerson, Alfred E., 1938-1947 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Endowed universities, 1938-1939 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Engberg, Edward, 1957-1969 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - English, 1939-1950 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Epstein, Max, 1933-1950 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Epstein, Max and Leola, 1951-1958 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Erb, Estelle Bood, 1939-1940 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Erickson and Erickson, 1938-1948 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Ernst, Fritz B., 1938 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Eurich, Alvin C., 1958-1969 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Evans, 1938-1950 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Evanston, 1938-1945 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Evarts, Effingham C., 1923-1926 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Ewald, William R., 1970-1976 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Ewing, Gifford C., 1930-1950 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Executives Club of Chicago, 1940-1950 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Experimental Schools, conference, 1967-1968 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Facci, Joseph, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Fackenthal, Frank D., 1949-1950 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Fadiman, Clifton, 1938-1948 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Fadiman, Clifton and Edwin, 1959-1965 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Fadiman, Clifton and Edwin, 1968-1977 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Faherty, Roger, 1943-1945 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Fairbank, Janet, 1941-1943 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Fairchild, 1938-1943 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Faris, Ellsworth, 1939-1950 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Farmer, 1939-1942 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Farnam, Thomas W., 1935-1943 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Farrand, Max, 1938-1941 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Farrar and Rinehart, 1938-1944 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Faust, Clarence and Gladys, 1954-1975 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Fay, 1939-1940 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Federal, 1942-1949 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 1935-1950 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Federal Projects, 1936-1939 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - General correspondence, 1933 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - Official correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - Official correspondence, 1933 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - Official correspondence, 1933 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - Official correspondence, 1933 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - Official correspondence, 1933 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - Official correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - Official correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Federal Unemployment Committee - Official correspondence, 1934 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Federations, 1938-1945 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Federations, 1938-1950 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Fehr, Joseph Conrad, 1941-1942 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Feldman, 1940 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1946-1950 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Fennelly, John F., 1938-1941 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Ferguson and Fergusson, 1939-1947 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Ferry, W. H., 1954-1963 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Ferry, W. H., 1964-1973 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Feller, Lewis S., 1941 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Field, 1938-1948 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Field, Marshall, 1933-1947 (Box 125, Folder 7)